seolinksubmission.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy :: Free Directory Submission, Free Link Directory, Free Web Directory, Add Your Web Site, Free Local Directory, Submit Your Url

| 

We respect our clients' right to privacy online. We hold detailed client information in confidence.

###  Asking For Your Information

####  [seolinksubmission](http://www.seolinksubmission.com/) will somedays  ask client for personal information such as name, e-mail address, address, occupation, and other details. Providing us your information will simply help us to offer products and services that we think you'd like to hear about. When you choose to give personal information to us over Internet that we or our business partners may request, we will endeavor to inform you how we will use this information. When we ask for your personal information for some reason, we will provide a link to this policy statement to make our intentions clear.

###  Personal Information Privacy

####  We will take all appropriate steps to keep your personal information secure. These steps include limiting access to clients information databases, communicating this policy statement to employees of the company and establishing and enforcing penalties for violating this statement. The company will not sell, rent, or give away its clients' personal information to other companies for enabling them to use it in selling other products or services.

####  When we do contract with other companies to market or advertise products or services for us, we will insist on binding agreements from those companies protecting our clients valuable information. We will vigorously enforce all privacy agreements that we have with other companies. We gather personal information from our clients so that we can develop better relationships with them. Occasionally, we seek clients comments on our products and services. These comments allow us to determine which products and services our clients should be made aware of based on their specific needs. 

####  We will communicate with clients via e-mail or other online delivery devices only if the client agrees to receive those communications. Clients, who believe they are receiving our communications in error or no longer desire to receive them, should inform us and we will remove those clients' names from our mailing lists. Our organization will be judicious in the use of e-mail and paper mail to communicate with clients. 

| 

Latest Comments 

Comment Author **jackmarkson0** / Jun 17, 2014 

Awesome Deals.. http://www.globester.com/

* * *

Comment Author **petergomes76webs** / Jun 5, 2014 

Best Website Design Company

* * *

Comment Author **Tyreonwheels** / May 29, 2014 

Awesome services........... given by tyreonwheels.com 

* * *

Comment Author **Andrew Boucher** / Mar 24, 2014 

Great information stuff here..! We got best results from there services to our websites. Thanks & Regards Andrew.

* * *

Comment Author **juneliao** / Feb 17, 2014 

Great website!  
  
---|---|---
